solo-e.com 2005-12-19

# Solo-E.com - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

**This privacy policy covers the site www.Solo-E.com and addresses:**

**1.** What personally identifiable information Solo-E.com collects.

**2.** What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Web site.

**3.** What organization collects the information.

**4.** How Solo-E.com uses the information.

**5.** With whom Solo-E.com may share user information.

**6.** What choices are available to users regarding collection, use, and distribution of the information.

**7.** What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of information under Solo-E.com control.

**8.** How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

If users have questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, they should first contact customer service: www.solo-e.com/feedback.

Solo-Entrepreneur.com respects each individual's right to personal privacy. We collect and use information through our Web site only in the ways disclosed in this policy statement. 

This statement, which details how we gather and disseminate information, has been drafted in an effort to demonstrate our strong commitment to YOUR privacy.

Solo-Entrepreneur.com, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on www.solo-e.com. Solo-Entrepreneur.com collects information from our users to pay for their membership, for our newsletter list, to send information to friends about the site, and in our discussion forums. 

Our membership software, forums and other site areas may require members to supply contact information, such as name and e-mail address, and demographic information, such as your address and phone number. We use this information solely to process payments, perform the services offered via the site and to be able to contact you regarding administration of those services. 

The contact information you provide is used solely to validate your interest and to provide you with the information you require. None of the information you submit will be used by Solo-E for any other reason,nor will it be sold to or shared with a third party.   

* * *

**System Files**

Cookies are currently used to manage login information and access to member only, protected areas. 

This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by Solo-E only and does not cover the use of cookies by any links or advertisers.

Like most standard Web site servers, we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

* * *

**Communications from the Site**

We send all new members a welcoming e-mail(s). Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see the Choice/Opt-out section. (If you are not receiving the emails you requested from Solo-E.com, please visit our [FAQs](http://www.solo-e.com/FAQ/faq.shtml) for possible solutions.)

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.

Solo-E does NOT share site usage information with third party advertisers.

Users who no longer wish to receive our announcements may opt-out of receiving these communications by clicking the unsubscribe link in any of the communications received.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the changes to this privacy policy, the homepage, and in other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

If, at any time, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via e-mail.

The privacy rights conferred by this Privacy Policy inure to the benefit of the individual users who contribute to Solo-E.com. Solo-Entrepreneur.com, Inc., reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy from time to time, but in no event may this privacy policy be modified to reduce the scope of the rights conferred to the users of this site. This Privacy Policy shall be binding upon Solo-Entrepreneur.com, Inc., its successors and assigns, and upon any third party that may later come into possession or control of the assets of Solo-Entrepreneur.com, Inc.

* * *

All material on these pages is owned by and all rights are reserved by Solo-Entrepreneur.com, Inc., for our use and reproduction, unless as otherwise indicated. This includes all text, images, structure and format, and the processes employed on this Web site. No part of these pages, either text or image may be used for any pourpose other than personal use. Therefore, reproduction, modification, storage in a retrieval system or retransmission, in any form or by any means, electronic, mechanical or otherwise, for reasons other than personal use, are strictly prohibited without prior written permission. 

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Solo-Entrepreneur.com, Inc. are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy policy of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend's name and e-mail address. Solo-E.com will automatically send the friend a one-time e-mail inviting them to visit the site. Solo-E.com temporarily stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail and tracking the success of our referral program. This information is not retained and will not be used for any subsequent programs offered by Solo-Entrepreneur.com, Inc. 

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through e-mail, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

All members shall be responsible for any messages posted in the Solo-E.com forum as well as be responsible for any consequences of messages transmitted. Solo-E.com reserves the right to remove any posts that violate guidelines set forth on the site. If necessary, Solo-E.com has the right to remove and/or deny access to community-related areas of the site to anyone who violates those guidelines. 

In submitting messages, members grant Solo-E.com a royalty-free, non-exclusive right and license to use, reproduce, edit, publish, distribute, and display the content of messages (in their entirety or partial) on the site or within other methods of communication. Therefore, we also allow others to access, view, and respond to messages.   

Members are solely responsible for maintaining the privacy of their personal information and password. Members will be responsible for all uses of their account and should ensure that unauthorized use is avoided by all reasonable means. In the event of unauthorized use, a member should contact Solo-E.com immediately at www.solo-e.com/feedback [security@solo-e.com](mailto:security@solo-e.com).

This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and offline.

If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can send an e-mail to [security@solo-e.com](mailto:security@solo-e.com).

Solo-Entrepreneur.com reserves the right, at our discretion, to suspend or terminate membership and services immediately and without notice, if any guidelines are violated.

Solo-Entrepreneur.com may modify the site guidelines as deemed appropriate by the site and site staff. A member agrees to have accepted these guidelines and any changes by interacting on the site. Changes to guidelines will, when possible, be communicated in advance to site users.

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

* * *
